scoopers.com 2013-05-20

# Scoopers - Share your passions, Photos, Videos, Music and Scoops in our Community

Sign up to post, share  
and vote for the best scoops.

Share your passions!

Privacy statement for Scoopers

Scoopers respects your privacy. Scoopers thus will carefully guard your personal data and we undertake to only use this data as described in this privacy statement, in accordance with applicable law.

General provisions

We process only the personal data you supply directly to us. This includes data sent by your web browser when requesting information from our website.  
Our web server registers general visitor data. This includes the IP-address of your computer, a user name (if applicable), the date and time of the request and other data sent by your browser. We register and use this information for statistical analysis of visitor and clickthrough behavior on our website. We will not supply visitor data of individual users to third parties.

Profile data and scoops

After registration we retain the personal data you provide, such as your name, e-mail address, profile information and information related to contributions (“scoops”) you make. You can adapt this data yourself through the website.

Data you enter or upload to Scoopers is published in the way you indicate. By default all information is public. You can change visibility of any information using the privacy settings. Information you mark private is only provided to third parties with your explicit consent or if required by law. 

Contributions that are made accessible to the public are also available to search engines and third parties that may copy and reuse them in ways Scoopers cannot control or prevent.

Advertising and profiling

Scoopers is offered to you free of charge. We use advertising to support Scoopers. To get the most effective return for advertisers, we adapt advertisements based on your profile. Advertisers do not get access to your profile as such; we select which of their advertisements to show. 

Advertisers do get access to aggregated visitor data so they can determine what kind of advertisements would be of interest to Scoopers. No data that is tracable to an individual is disclosed.

Use of cookies

Scoopers uses cookies. A cookie is a small file that is delivered together with pages from this website and which your browser stores on the hard disk of your computer. The cookie allows us to combine separate visits to the website and analyze the behavior of individual users. You can block or refuse the use of cookies, although this may negatively affect the functioning and the usability of the website.

After logging in with your username and password our website sends you a cookie in order to recognize you for the rest of your session. This cookie allows us to record which pages you request as a logged-in user. If you block this cookie you cannot use the website.

E-mail and newsletters

If you send mail to Scoopers or use one of the contact or subscription forms provided on the website, then we will retain the data included therein for as long as necessary to process the form or mail and provide you with a suitable response.

Scoopers operates an e-mail newsletter to inform interested parties about updates and relevant news. Your e-mail address will only be included on the distribution list with your explicit consent. Every issue of the newsletter will include an unsubscription hyperlink. The subscription user base will not be made available to third parties.

Security

Scoopers uses strict security procedures, among others to guard against unauthorized access to personal data. In particular we strive to use secured connections (Secure Sockets Layer or SSL) to protect all transmissions of information between you and us during registration or when you provide personal or financial data.

Data inspection, changes and deletion

You have the legal right to request inspection, correction or deletion of any personal data we retain regarding you. Most of your personal data can be changed or deleted using your profile page. For other changes or deletions, or for inspection of other data, please contact us through the website.

Scoopers may choose not remove certain contributions, if such removal would render contributions of others incomprehensible. In such a case the contribution will be anonymized.

Third-party websites

This privacy statement does not apply to third-party websites that are connected to this website using hyperlinks. Scoopers cannot guarantee that these third parties respect your privacy and recommends that you read their privacy statements before using these websites.

Changes to this privacy statement

Scoopers reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time. Scoopers will give at least fourteen days’ notice by means of an announcement on Scoopers.

Scoops

Members

Pages

Comments

Votes

Contact

Contact us if you have any questions, we will get back to you as quickly as possible.
